PAWEŁ CZYŻ

Automation Developer Wrocław, Poland

Contact: pawel.czyz89@gmail.com

Detail oriented Automation Developer. Experienced in the business process analysis, automation and improvement. Saving time and increasing processes quality with RPA platforms (Blue Prism, UiPath) and software development (Visual Basic for Applications, C# .Net, SQL). Bringing Digital Transformation to F&A, HR and Payroll processes.

EXPERIENCE

DXC TECHNOLOGY

February 2019-Present

BUSINESS PROCESS IMPROVEMENT SPECIALIST

Role: Automation Developer

In this role I am a part of a team driving digitalization and automation of business processes across variety of domains and target systems. I handle RPA implementation process - from request to assessment, to PDD, design and development through testing and corrections, deployment, hyper-care, maintenance, change requests and improvements.

My daily tasks include:

- Design, development and deployment of RPA solutions (Blue Prism, UiPath, WinAutomation)
- Applications and tools development (VBA,C# .Net)
- Maintenance of already implemented applications and solutions
- Continuous improvement process
- Processing Change Requests
- Resolving application-related incidents and issues
- End user support
- Active participation in process optimization and simplification

DXC TECHNOLOGY

October 2017-January 2019

BUSINESS PROCESS ANALYST

Role: VBA Developer

As a Business Process Analyst I was primarly resposible for identification and implementation of improvements in F&A, HR and Payroll processes. These improvements usually took a form of automation tools developed in VBA (Excel, Access, Outlook, Word, PowerPoint as well and web automation in IE). I was also processing mass changes in SAP using GUI Scripting and Innowera Process Runner. Other resposibilities included maintenance and support of legacy tools (C# .Net and VBA), monthly and ad-hoc reporting. I also took active part in tools migration from local environment to virtual desktop infrastructure (Citrix).

Types of tools created:

- Vendor Master Data change requests tracker (VBA Excel and Access)
- WebForm filling tools (VBA Excel and IE)
- Quality control tools (VBA Excel and SAP reports)
- Word letters creating tool (VBA Excel and Word)
- Reporting tools with email notifications (VBA Excel and Outlook)
- Workflow management tools (VBA Excel and Access)
- Monthly PowerPoint presentation tools (VBA Excel and PowerPoint)

Achievements:

- Received Certificate of Appreciation for time saving generated with SAP GUI Scripting
- Initiated VBA Training Group for colleagues interested in self development

3M GSC Poland

September 2016-September 2017

STP JUNIOR ANALYST

Role: Accounts Payable UK/IE Analyst

As an STP Analyst I was responsible for processing invoices, handling email and phone queries from vendors, processing vendor master data change requests (banking details and payment terms) and daily reporting. I managed to create several reporting automation tools in VBA. I also created scripts in SAP GUI Scripting enabling automated invoice posting for several vendors, reducing manual workload and improving processing quality.

EY GDS

December 2014-August 2016

ACCOUNTING ASSOCIATE

Role: Accounts Payable GSA Specialist

As an Accounting Associate I was responsible for processing around two thousand invoices per month. My main tasks included invoice indexing, approval workflow, posting to PeopleSoft and SAP and finally payment creation in banking tool. I was also responsible for vendor accounts creation and maintenance. I took active part in migration from PeopleSoft to SAP. I proved to be proactive, reliable and versatile employee acting not only as accounts payable specialist but also reporting specialist, SAP SuperUser and IT support.

Achievements:

- Extra miler award for the involvement in the preparation of vendor database for the conversion to SAP system
- Extra miler award for the involvement in the IT-related issues solving

TECH SKILLS

- Blue Prism
- UiPath (Certified RPA Developer)
- Visual Basic for Applications (advanced)
- C# and .Net Framework
- HTML, CSS and JavaScript (basics)
- · SQL
- WinAutomation
- Abbyy FlexiCapture
- AutoHotkey
- Visual Studio
- SQL Server Management Studio
- · Git and GitHub
- Microsoft Azure

EDUCATION

University of Technology Master's degree (2008–2013) **Logistics**

Yasar University Erasmus Programme (2012) **Green Logistics**

University of Technology Bachelor's degree (2011–2014) **Business English**

SOFT SKILLS

- Fast learning and well developed analytical thinking, design thinking and problem solving skills
- Communication skills ability to present complex technical solutions in a clear and easy to undarstand way
- Self-motivation, accountability and time management skills

LANGUAGES

English – Bachelor's degree **Polish** – Native